Disney+ gets wild.
The Ice Age Adventures of Buck Wild is a animation,
comedy, family film directed by John C. Donkin.
The fearless one-eyed weasel Buck teams up with mischievous possum brothers Crash & Eddie
as they head off on a new adventure into Buck's home: The Dinosaur World.
Buck (voice), played by Simon Pegg.
Crash (voice), played by Vincent Tong.
Eddie (voice), played by Aaron Harris.
Orson (voice), played by Utkarsh Ambudkar.
Zee (or whatever her name is) (voice), played by Justina Machado.
Manny (voice), played by Sean Kenin.
The Ice Age Adventures of Buck Wild is a 2022 animated
adventure comedy film directed by John C.
Donkin, in his feature directorial debut, with a screenplay by Jim Hecht, Ray
DeLaurentis, and William Schifrin based on a story written by Hecht.
It is a spin-off film of the Ice Age franchise,
and the sixth overall installment.
The film stars the voices of Simon Pegg (the only previous cast member to return), Vincent Tong,
Aaron Harris, Utkarsh Ambudkar, and Justina Machado also starring in the film.
It follows the two opossum brothers Crash and Eddie and their adventure to
becoming independent possums alongside the titular character Buck Wild.
Originally planned to be a television series, The Ice Age Adventures of
Buck Wild was redeveloped into a feature-length film.
Produced by 20th Century Animation and released under the Walt Disney Pictures
banner, it was released on January 28, 2022 as a Disney+ original film.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of ice age, snow, spin off, polar adventure.
The tone is lighthearted.